Guide to the BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1)
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1)
- Series IX: Industry Code #44, Retail Trade
  - Code no.6788: Food Retailers Association of the Greater New York Trading Area and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 342, 1970-1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Item 2: Food Retailers Association of the Greater New York Trading Area and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Retail Food Stores Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 342, 1972-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 6/26/1972 and expires on 8/25/1973. Covers 6000 workers in Richmond Co., NY; Kings Co., NY; Queens Co., NY; Nassau Co., NY; Suffolk Co., NY
  - Code no.6794: Specialty Bakery Owners of America, Inc. and Retail Clerks International Association, Local 1111, 1965-1968 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Specialty Bakery Owners of America, Inc. and Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 1111, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 2/1/1965 and expires on 1/31/1968. Covers 1200 workers in New York, NY
  - Code no.6910: San Francisco Retailers Council and Retail Shoe and Textile Salesmen's Union, Local 410, 1958-1961 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: San Francisco Retailers Council and Retail Shoe and Textile Salesmen's Union, AFL-CIO, Local 410, 1958-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 10/15/1958 and expires on 5/31/1961. Covers an unknown number of workers in San Francisco, CA
    - Item 2: San Francisco Retailers Council and Retail Shoe and Textile Salesmen's Union, AFL-CIO, Local 410 Addendum, 1959-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 6/1/1959 and expires on 6/1/1961. Covers an unknown number of workers in San Francisco, CA
  - Code no.6902: Greater St. Louis Automotive Association, Inc. and ST. Clair-Madison Automotive Association, Inc. and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District No. 9, 1970-1976 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Greater St. Louis Automotive Association, Inc. and St. Clair-Madison Automotive Association, Inc. and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 9, 1970-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 8/1/1970 and expires on 7/31/1973. Covers 2450 workers in St. Louis, MO; IL
    - Item 2: Greater St. Louis Automotive Association, Inc. and St. Clair-Madison Automotive Association, Inc. and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 9, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 8/1/1973 and expires on 7/31/1976. Covers an unknown number of workers in St. Louis, MO; IL
  - Code no.6905: Standard Stations, Inc. and Western States Service Station Employees Union, 1967-1977 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Standard Stations, Inc. and Western States Service Employees Union, 1967-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 4/15/1967 and expires on 4/15/1968. Covers an unknown number of workers in San Francisco, CA
    - Item 2: Standard Stations, Inc. and Western States Service Employees Union, 1969-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 4/16/1969 and expires on 4/15/1970. Covers 5969 workers in San Francisco, CA
    - Item 3: Standard Stations, Inc. and Western States Service Employees Union, 1970-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 4/16/1970 and expires on 4/15/1971. Covers 4798 workers in San Francisco, CA
    - Item 4: Standard Stations, Inc. and Western States Service Employees Union, 1971-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1971 and expires on 4/1/1973. Covers 3034 workers in San Francisco, CA
    - Item 5: Standard Stations, Inc. and Western States Service Employees Union, 1973-1975; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1973 and expires on 4/1/1975. Covers 2694 workers in San Francisco, CA
    - Item 6: Standard Stations, Inc. and Western States Service Employees Union, 1975-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1975 and expires on 4/1/1976. Covers 1524 workers in San Francisco, CA
    - Item 7: Standard Stations, Inc. and Western States Service Employees Union Addendum, 1976-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1976 and expires on 4/1/1977. Covers an unknown number of workers in San Francisco, CA
  - Code no.6912: "Popular Priced Chain Stores" and Retail Shoe Employees Union, Locals 287 and 1268, 1962-1967 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Chain Stores and Retail Shoe Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Locals 1268 and 287, 1962-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 8/1/1962 and expires on 7/31/1964. Covers 1200 workers in New York, NY; Nassau Co., NY; Suffolk Co., NY
    - Item 2: Miles Shoe Company, National Shoe Company, and Simco Shoe Company and Retail Shoe Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Locals 1268 and 287, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 8/3/1964 and expires on 7/31/1967. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY; Nassau Co., NY; Suffolk Co., NY
  - Code no.6914: Chicago Metropolitan Automobile Dealers Association and Independent Dealers and Automobile Mechanics' Local 701, 1973- 1975 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Chicago Metropolitan Automobile Dealers Association and Independent Dealers and Automobile Mechanics, AFL-CIO, Local 701, 1971-1975; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1971 and expires on 7/1/1975. Covers an unknown number of workers in Chicago, IL
  - Code no.6915: Independent Service Station Operators and International Brotherhood of Service Station Operators of America, 1971- 1974 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Independent Service Station Operators and International Brotherhood of Service Station Operators of America, 1971-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 12/17/1971 and expires on 12/17/1974. Covers 1202 workers in Whittier, CA
  - Code no.7301: New York Retail Druggists Association and Drug and Hospital Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 1199, 1961-1966 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: New York Retail Druggists Association and Drug and Hospital Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 1199, 1961-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1961 and expires on 9/30/1963. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York
    - Item 2: New York Retail Druggists Association and Drug and Hospital Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 1199, 1963-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1963 and expires on 9/30/1966. Covers 750 workers in New York
  - Code no.7302-1: Seattle-King County Retail Druggists Association and Retail Clerks Union, Local 330, 1960-1962 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Seattle-King County Pharmaceutical Society and Seattle Retail Drug Distributors Association and Pharmacists and Retail Drug Stores Employees Union, Local 330, 1960-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 9/16/1960 and expires on 9/15/1962. Covers 1300 workers in Seattle, WA
    - Item 2: Seattle-King County Pharmaceutical Society and Seattle Retail Drug Distributors Association and Pharmacists and Retail Clerks Union, Local 330, 1960-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1960 and expires on 9/1/1962. Covers an unknown number of workers in Seattle, WA
  - Code no.7302-2: Seattle-King County Pharmaceutical Society and the Seattle Retail Drug Association and Pharmacists and Retail Drug Store Employees Union, Local 330, AFL-CIO, 1962-1968 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Seattle-King County Pharmaceutical Society and Seattle Retail Drug Distributors Association and Pharmacists and Retail Drug Stores Employees Union, Local 330, 1962-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 9/16/1962 and expires on 9/15/1964. Covers 1400 workers in Seattle, WA
    - Item 2: Seattle-King County Pharmaceutical Society and Seattle Retail Drug Distributors Association and Pharmacists and Retail Drug Stores Employees Union, Local 330, 1964-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 10/25/1964 and expires on 9/30/1968. Covers 1700 workers in Seattle, WA
  - Code no.7302-3: Seattle-King County Pharmaceutical Society and the Seattle Retail Drug Association and Pharmacists and Retail Drug Store Employees Union, Local 330, AFL-CIO, 1968-1970 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: Seattle-King County Pharmaceutical Society and The Greater Seattle Retail Drug Association, Inc. and Pharmacists and Retail Drug Stores Employees Union, Local 330, 1968-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1968 and expires on 9/30/1970. Covers 2200 workers in Seattle, WA
    - Item 2: Seattle-King County Pharmaceutical Society and The Greater Seattle Retail Drug Association, Inc. and Pharmacists and Retail Drug Stores Employees Union, Local 330, 1968-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Code no.7304-1: Metropolitan Package Store Association, Inc. and Wine and Liquor Store Employees Union, Local 122, AFL-CIO, 1960- 1970 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Metropolitan Package Store Association, Inc. and Wine and Liquor Store Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 122, 1960-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1960 and expires on 12/31/1962. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 2: Metropolitan Package Store Association, Inc. and Wine and Liquor Store Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 122, 1964-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1964 and expires on 12/31/1966. Covers 2000 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 3: No employer specified and Wine and Liquor Store Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 122, 1967-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1967 and expires on 12/31/1967. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 4: Metropolitan Package Store Association, Inc. and Wine and Liquor Store Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 122, 1968-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1968 and expires on 12/31/1970. Covers 933 workers in New York, NY
  - Code no.7961: Metropolitan Chicago Car Wash-Gasoline Service Station Employers and Truck Drivers, Oil Drivers, Filling Station and Platform Workers' Union, Local 705 of International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1967-1970 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Car Wash-Gasoline Service Station Employers of Metropolitan Chicago and Truck Drivers, Oil Drivers, Filling Station and Platform Workers Union, Local 705, 1967-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1967 and expires on 10/31/1970. Covers 1500 workers in Chicago, IL
  - Code no.6798 / 591021: Daitch Crystal Dairies, Inc. and Retail, Wholesale, and Chain Store Food Employees Union, Local 338, 1966- 1972 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Daitch Crystal Dairies, Inc. and Retail, Wholesale and Chain Store Food Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 338, 1966-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1966 and expires on 12/31/1968. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY; Nassau Co., NY; Suffolk Co., NY; Westchester Co., NY; Rockland Co., NY; Ulster Co., NY; Sullivan Co., NY
    - Item 2: Daitch Crystal Dairies, Inc. and Retail, Wholesale and Chain Store Food Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 338, 1969-1972; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 3/12/1969 and expires on 1/31/1972. Covers 1000 workers in New York, NY; Nassau Co., NY; Suffolk Co., NY; Westchester Co., NY; Rockland Co., NY; Ulster Co., NY; Sullivan Co., NY
- Series X: Industry Code #45, Retail Trade
  - Code no.6500-1: Bloomingdale Brother and Bloomingdale Department Store Employees Union, Local 3, 1950-1962 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Code no.6503-1: Marshall Field and Company and Sales Services Union, Local 372, 1960-1967 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    1960- 1962, 1966-1967
  - Code no.6504: Gimbel Brothers, Inc. and United Storeworkers Union, Local 2, 1973-1977 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Code no.6508: Macy's New York and Retail, Wholesale, Department Store Workers Union, AFL-CIO, Local 1-S, 1970-1976 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Code no.6509: Montgomery Ward and Co. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 294, 1958-1963 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Code no.6510: Montgomery Ward and Co. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 743, 1958-1963 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Code no.6511: Montgomery Ward and Co. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 452, 1958-1963 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Code no.6512: Montgomery Ward and Co. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 590, 1963-1967 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Code no.6513-1: San Francisco Retailers Council and Department Store Employees' Union, Local 1100, 1958-1964 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Code no.6513-2: San Francisco Retailers Council and Department Store Employees' Union, Local 1100, 1965-1972 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Code no.6518: Aldens, Inc. and Warehouse and Mail Order Employees Union, Local 743, 1960-1969 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Code no.6519-1: Montgomery Ward and Co. and Warehouse, Retail, and Mail Order Employees, Local 794, 1958-1967 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Code no.6520: Montgomery Ward and Co. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 452, 1958-1963 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Code no.6520-2: Montgomery Ward and Co. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 452, 1963-1967 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Code no.6521-1: Montgomery Ward and Co. and Warehouse, Retail, and Mail Order Employees, Local 743, 1963-1967 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Code no.6522: Montgomery Ward and Co. and Warehouse, Mail Order and Distribution Workers, Local 838, 1958-1967 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Code no.6524: Montgomery Ward and Co. and Warehouse Employees Union, Local 590, 1958-1967 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Code no.6525: Spiegel, Inc. and Warehouse and Mail Order Employees Union, Local 743, 1958-1971 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Code no.6526-1: Montgomery Ward and Co. and Retail Clerks Union, Locals 1512A and 876, 1958-1963 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Code no.6527: Freight Checkers, Traffic Clerks and Clerical Employees and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 342, 1961- 1963 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Code no.6529: Jordan Marsh Company and Retain Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 1291, 1963-1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Code no.6530: Montgomery Ward and Co. and Mail Order Retail Department Store and Warehouse Employees Local Union 149, affiliated with the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1963-1968 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Code no.6531: Lit Brothers, Division of City Stores and Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Code no.6533: Spiegel, Inc. and Warehouse and Mail Order Employees Union, Local 743, 1966-1969 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Code no.6537: Yankee Distributors, Inc. and Central States Joint Board, Retail and Department Store Employees, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1967-1973 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Code no.6544: Sears, Roebuck, and Co. and Department Store Employees Union, Local 1100, 1964-1975 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Code no.7307-1: Los Angeles White Front Stores and Retail Clerks Union, Local 770, 1962-1967 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Code no.7900-1: Direct Mail Master Contract Association and Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, AFL-CIO, District 65, 1959- 1962 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Code no.7900-2: Direct Mail Master Contract Association and Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, AFL-CIO, District 65, 1962- 1968 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Series XI: Industry Code #48, Transportation and Warehousing
  - Code no.5022-1: Transport of New Jersey and Amalgamated Transit Union, Locals 819, 820, 821, 822, 823, 824, 825, 880, 1974- 1978 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Code no.5033-2: Greyhound Lines, Inc. and Amalgamated Transit Union, AFL-CIO, Divisions 1042, 1043, 1063, 1098, 1201, 1202, 1203, 1205, 1210, 1211, 1303, 1516, 1966-1974 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Code no.5244: Maryland-District of Columbia and National Over-The-Road and City Cartage Policy and Negotiating Committee, 1970- 1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Code no.5276-1: Tri-Area Labor Association, Philadelphia and Vicinity and National Over-The-Road and City Cartage Policy and Negotiating Committee, 1970-1976 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Code no.5403-1: Dry Cargo and Passenger Companies and International Organization of Masters, Mates, and Pilots, 1961-1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    1961-1965, 1972-1975
  - Code no.5424-2: Pacific Maritime Association and International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, 1961-1971 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Code no.6311-1: Oil, Petroleum, Chemicals and Liquid Products Drivers and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 301, 1970- 1976 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Code no.6311-2: Oil, Petroleum, Chemicals and Liquid Products Drivers and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Locals 301, 673, 705, 179, 1976-1979 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Code no.7305-1: Chicago Coal Merchants Association and Coal Drivers, Helpers, Handlers and Allied Industries Union, Local 704, affiliated with International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1961-1967 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Code no.7910: Pacific Airmotive Corporation and International Association of Machinists, AFL-CIO, District 727, 120, 727F, 749, 1960- 1962 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Code no.7985: Metropolitan Marine Maintenance Contractors' Association, Inc. and International Longshoremen's Association, AFL-CIO, Locals 1277 and 1804, 1961-1966 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Series XII: Industry Code #49, Transportation and Warehousing
  - Code no.399: Watsonville Employers Frozen Food Association and California State Council of Freezer Unions, Local 912, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers, 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Code no.6331-1: Industrial Employers and Distributors Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Locals 12, 287, 315, 655, 853, 860, 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Series XIII: Industry Code #51, Information
  - Code no.5731: Michigan Bell Telephone Company and Communications Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1971-1977 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Code no.5741-1: New Jersey Bell Telephone Company and Communications Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1967-1974 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Code no.5751-1: Pacific Telephone and Bell of Nevada and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1011, 1971-1977 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Code no.5752-1: Pacific Telephone and Bell of Nevada and Communications Workers of America, 1971-1977 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Code no.5753-5: Pacific Northwest Bell and Communications Workers of America, 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Code no.5759: Pacific Telephone and Bell of Nevada and Federation of Women Telephone Workers of Southern California, 1971- 1974 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Code no.5778-2: Western Union Telegraph Company and Commercial Telegraphers' Union, AFL-CIO, 1962-1964 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Code no.5778-3: Western Union Telegraph Company and Commercial Telegraphers' Union, AFL-CIO, 1964-1966 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Code no.5778-6: Western Union Telegraph Company and United Telegraph Workers, AFL-CIO, 1973-1976 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Code no.5778-4: Western Union Telegraph Company and United Telegraph Workers, AFL-CIO, 1966-1971 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Code no.5778-5: Western Union Telegraph Company and United Telegraph Workers, AFL-CIO, 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Code no.7912: Columbia Pictures, Loew's Incorporated, Paramount Pictures, Republic Productions, RKO Radio Pictures, Warner Bros. Pictures, Twentieth Century Fox Film Co. and Universal Pictures and Screen Actors Guild, 1952-1965 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Code no.7913: (Employer not listed) and International Hod Carriers, Building and Common Laborers Union, Local 724, 1961-1963 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Code no.7914-1: Alliance of Television Film Producers, Inc. and Screen Directors' Guild of America, 1958-1960 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Code no.7914-2: Association of Motion Picture and Television Producers, Inc. and Screen Directors' Guild of America, 1964-1972 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Code no.7915-2: Association of Motion Picture and Television Producers, Inc. and International Alliance of Theatrical State Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators, Locals 659, 80, 729, 706, 816, 871, 695, 876, 1965-1979 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Code no.7915-1: Motion Picture Producers and Laboratories and International Alliance of Theatrical State Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators, Locals 44, 80, 165, 468, 659, 683, 695, 705, 706, 727, 728, 729, 767, 776, 789, 790, 816, 839, 847, 81, 1961-1966 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Code no.7916-1: Employer Groups and Studio Transportation Drivers, Local 399 of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1969- 1973 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Code no.7917: Film Producers Association of New York and International Alliance of Theatrical State Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada, AFL- CIO, 1958-1960 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Code no.7918: Independent Motion Picture Producers and American Federation of Musicians, 1960-1964 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Code no.7919-1: Television and Radio Commercial Announcements Agreement and American Federation of Musicians, 1959-1969 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Code no.7920-2: Association of Motion Picture and Television Producers, Inc. and Screen Actors Guild, 1971-1977 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Code no.7921-1: AFM Basic Theatrical Motion Picture and American Federation of Musicians, 1961-1972 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Code no.7922: Independent Motion Picture Industry Employer and International Alliance of Theatrical and Stage Employees, 1958- 1966 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Code no.7923: Motion Picture Service Industry (Film Processing), New York and New Jersey and Motion Picture Laboratory Technicians, Local 702, 1959-1968 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Code no.7946: Employees in Los Angeles County; Independent Producers and American Federation of Musicians of the United States and Canada, 1964-1974 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Code no.7950: Independent Producers and Writers Guild of America, 1956-1973 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Code no.7956: MGM, Paramount, 20th Century Fox, United Artists, Universal, Columbia, Buena Vista, National Film Service, Bonded Film Service, National Screen Service and International Alliance of Theatrical State Employees and Moving Picture Machine Opera, 1966-1968 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Code no.7958: ABC, CBS, NBC radio-television networks, makers of commercials and Screen Actors Guild, 1966-1970 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Series XIV: Industry Code #52, Finance and Insurance
  - Code no.7400-1: American National Insurance Company and Insurance Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, 1960-1962 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Code no.7400-2: American National Insurance Company and Insurance Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, 1962-1974 (Box 11, Folder 19)